{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Hutton",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1737-08-14",
    "human_readable": "Charles Hutton was born on 14th August 1737.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8637555241584778,
            "question": "When was Charles Hutton born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7962815761566162,
            "question": "Where was Charles Hutton born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5634245276451111,
            "question": "What is Charles Hutton known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5034862756729126,
            "question": "In what year did Charles Hutton's life begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4906158149242401,
            "question": "Who were some of Charles Hutton's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36046087741851807,
            "question": "Was Charles Hutton involved in any significant scientific societies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29502221941947937,
            "question": "What field of study is Charles Hutton associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24363866448402405,
            "question": "What contributions did Charles Hutton make to mathematics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23555277287960052,
            "question": "Did Charles Hutton write any influential books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19920694828033447,
            "question": "What impact did Charles Hutton have on the development of science and mathematics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Hutton was born on 14th August 1737.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2993_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Charles Hutton write any influential books?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2993_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What contributions did Charles Hutton make to mathematics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2993_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field of study is Charles Hutton associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2993_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2993_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is a simple statement, and the answer should be either \"yes\" or \"no\". Here's the JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The documents confirm that Charles Hutton was born on 14 August 1737."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide consistent information that Charles Hutton was indeed born on 14th August 1737, as mentioned in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}